Contact

ulrike.beelar@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ulrikebeelar (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Emergency Room

PALS

ACLS

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
German (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Nurse Executive Advanced (NEA-BC)
CEN

Ulrike Beelar

Director of Emergency Services at Memorial Hermann Health System

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced healthcare leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Management, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Disaster Response, Emergency Medicine, and TNCC. Strong information technology professional with a Master of Science (MS) focused in Nursing Leadership and Management from Western Governors University, Texas.

Experience

Memorial Hermann Health System 4 years 6 months

Director Of Emergency Services August 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months) The Woodlands

Operations Administrator December 2015 - August 2017 (1 year 9 months)

The Woodlands

Harris Health System

7 years 8 months

Nursing Clinical Manager May 2013 - August 2017 (4 years 4 months)

Ben Taub Hospital, Emergency Center

Charge Nurse January 2010 - May 2013 (3 years 5 months)

Education

Western Governors University, Texas

Master of Science (MS), Nursing Leadership and Management · (2015)

Page 1 of 2

Western Governors University, Texas Bachelor's of science, Nursing · (2013)

Houston Community College Associate's degree, Nursing · (2007)